prima-coffee.com 2017-04-03

# Prima Coffee Equipment's Privacy Policy | Prima Coffee

## Welcome!

You are most likely visiting this page for one of two reasons: (1) you want to know what type of information we collect and how it is used, if this is you then congrats you are in the right place, please keep reading, or (2) you are lost, in which case you can click the following button to return to our home page:

Prima Coffee is committed to the privacy of your personal, identifiable information. We, like you, don’t like it when people sell or trade personal information in order to make a few bucks. In order to establish and maintain a trusting relationship with you, we are careful to protect all information you supply through our website and through our customer service team. This privacy policy works in conjunction with our internal corporate practices to protect you and your personal information from misuse. Please review our policy and contact our office with questions or concerns.

### What information do we collect?

We collect personal information, including your email address, phone number, credit card number, shipping and billing information, etc. This information is necessary in order to process your order, provide you with customer support, give you access to your order status and history, to send you email updates about your order, and to send occasional promotional emails (you may unsubscribe from these emails at any time by following the instructions on the bottom of the email message).

### Do we use cookies?

Everyone likes cookies, computers too, so when you visit our site we will feed your computer a cookie to help us remember the items in your cart, process your order, save your preferences for future visits, and gather anonymous usage data so that we can improve our services.

We also serve Google's double click script to enable remarketing campaigns that serve customized ads through Google's display network. You can opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCg4VHd0m21adYaAg9yNDxJFQTiTSdorWliAwloVbVUTgmchctwp2GJgAjNVdX5eTnvU_liK7Nw1FGvAO2MinLUps2ts4sc__SSyVF7FCU6gglVus727677iacDuZaJDGl9s2vkWKy9gmbFnJTyVHgeNeMVjqG3WCh_5C10Gqr73KbdwD0__6mf5ax3UV_6tHffg9HzX)

Some site functionality, is provided by approved third party vendors. In order to provide there service they set their own cookies and collect data. How they use that data is governed by their respective privacy policies. The third party services that we use and links to their privacy policies can be found below along with opt out links and a brief description of the service they provide.

##### Bazaar Voice

  * Description: Bazaar Voice provides Question and Answer and Review functionality.

##### Add This

  * Description: AddThis powers our social interaction buttons.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

Prima Coffee may disclose information we collect to our vendor partners who are directly involved in completing your order, including payment processors, shipping carriers, etc. We may also disclose information we collect when required by applicable law.

We promise to not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer personally identifiable information that we collect from you to an outside organization for their own use. What you give to us, stays with us, it is that simple.

Aggregate anonymous usage statistics may be used by Prima Coffee or our partners in order to improve our website and the services we offer.

### Business Transfers

If Prima Coffee, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Prima Coffee goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets transferred to the acquiring party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Prima Coffee may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their user account and going to the ‘edit’ page.

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](https://prima-coffee.com/pc/policy/tos) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <https://prima-coffee.com/pc/policy/tos>.

### Governing Policies

Your visit to and interaction with Prima Coffee is governed by the Terms of Use, Return Policy, Shipping Policy, Privacy Policy, and Pricing Policy which are posted on this site. These policies, along with our Glossary of Terms govern your visit to Prima Coffee. We reserve the right to make changes to our site and policies, at any time without any prior notification.

### Opt Out

You may choose to opt out at any time from receiving any further promotional material, newsletters, or any non-order related communication from us by using the email address listed below.

### Contacting Us

There you go, that’s it, but if you have any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

**This policy was last modified on _June 12, 2012_**
